Leonard Scott Union Prevention and Counter-Union Campaign Consulting Files 6474
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- National Labor Relations Board (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Local 745, IBT v NLRB, Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 15)
    61 LRRM pp. 2065-2066. Photocopies.
  - Item 3: Review of NLRB on Election Campaigns, Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 15)
    pp.170-172. Photocopies.
- Leonard Scott and Company Counter Union Campaign Material Samples (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Samples of Counter- Union Campaign materials Leonard Scott & Company has used in recent Chicago area assignments., Text (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Leonard Scott: Running a Struck Plant: Some Do's and Don'ts (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Running a Struck Plant: Some Do's and Don'ts, 1973; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    S.A.M. Advanced Management Journal. Vol. 38, Number 4. 1973, October.
- Leonard Scott: A New Look at Unionism (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: A New Look at Unionism, 1985; Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
    August 1985.
- Leonard Scott: A New Look at Unionism (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: A New Look at Unionism, 1985; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    In Fire Protection Contraction. Vol. 1, No. 11. November 1985.
- Leonard Scott: The Human Resources Program in the Growth Company (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: The Human Resources Program in the Growth Company, 1985; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
    In Fire Protection Contraction. Vol.8, No. 12. December 1985.
- Leonard Scott: Inclusive Capitalism: What It Looks Like in Practice (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Inclusive Capitalism: What It Looks Like in Practice, 2013; Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Self-published book by Leonard C. Scott.
- Leonard Scott: The Quick Guide to Employee Motivation: Thirty-Three Proven Employee Motivation Concepts to Make Your Company a Winner (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: The Quick Guide to Employee Motivation: Thirty-Three Proven Employee Motivation Concepts to Make Your Company a Winner, 2013; Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Maintaining Your Union-Free Status (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: WCIRA, SERA, MERA "Maintaining Your Union-Free Status" Brochure, Pamphlet (Box 1, Folder 23)
    West Coast Industrial Relations Association (WCIRA); Southwest Employee Relations Association (SERA); Mid-America Employee Relations Association.